vps6.net 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy \\ VPS6.NET

_Other than as described in this Policy, we will not give any information about you to others without your express permission._

#### Information Collection and Use

Our website uses forms, the purpose of which is to collect contact information (including your name, address, telephone number, and email address) so you can place orders and request information or support. For certain services, we may also request a credit card number, government identification number, or other financial information.

We receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way, including through email, telephone, or other communications with our customer service department. If you contact us for support, we will keep an internal record of what support was given.

We use your information to contact you regarding changes to our products, our website, new services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, please see the "Updating Your Information" section below on how to change your preferences.

We use information gathered about you from our website statistics (for example, your IP address) to help diagnose problems with our webserver, and to administer our website. We also gather broad demographic information from this data to help us improve our website and make your experience more enjoyable. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information, except as necessary to prevent fraud or abuse on our system.

Our website uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and receipts. We use cookies to identify you so you don't need to log in each time you visit our website. The cookies are linked to your customer number, which is associated with the information in your account.

This website also contains links to other websites. VPS6.NET is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

#### Updating Your Information

You may alter your account information or opt out of receiving communications from us at any time. You may update your account and contact information from within the Client Area ([my.vps6.net](https://my.vps6.net/)).

We use emails to communicate with you, to confirm your placed orders, and to send information that you have requested. We also provide email links to allow you to contact us directly. We strive to deliver prompt replies to all messages received.

The information you send to us may be stored and used to improve this website and our products, or it may be reviewed and discarded. 

#### What Happens to my Personal Information if I Terminate my client account?

When your VPS6 account is canceled (either voluntarily or involuntarily) all of your personally identifiable information is placed in "deactivated" status in our databases. However, deactivation of your account does not mean that your personally identifiable information has been permanently deleted from our database. We will retain and use your personally identifiable information, if necessary, in order to comply with our legal obligations, to resolve disputes, or to enforce our agreements. 

#### Changes in Our Practices

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy and any other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

If we make material changes to this Policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page, at least thirty (30) days prior to the implementation of the changes. 

#### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, the practices of VPS6.NET, or your dealings with VPS6.NET, please [contact us](https://my.vps6.net/contact.php).
